<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[My Blog]]></title>
  <link href="http://mariapichon.github.io/MyBlog/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://mariapichon.github.io/MyBlog/"/>
  <updated>2015-09-10T14:42:42-05:00</updated>
  <id>http://mariapichon.github.io/MyBlog/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Maria Isabel Pichon Cadena]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to My Blog]]></title>
    <link href="http://mariapichon.github.io/MyBlog/blog/2015/09/09/welcome-to-my-blog/"/>
    <updated>2015-09-09T16:17:15-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://mariapichon.github.io/MyBlog/blog/2015/09/09/welcome-to-my-blog</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Hi my name is Maria Isabel</p>

<!--more-->


<p>I&rsquo;m Mexican!</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Goodbye]]></title>
    <link href="http://mariapichon.github.io/MyBlog/blog/2015/08/28/goodbye/"/>
    <updated>2015-08-28T16:08:26-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://mariapichon.github.io/MyBlog/blog/2015/08/28/goodbye</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>It has been really interesting being part of the YWeb Cohort #2, and it&rsquo;s really sad to say goodbye to all my classmates and friends. Hopefully we will stay in touch and have meetings from time to time. Our last week of class was very interesting. Having group standups on google hangouts was an amazing experience although a bit weird since I don&rsquo;t like being on camera.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ruby]]></title>
    <link href="http://mariapichon.github.io/MyBlog/blog/2015/08/24/ruby/"/>
    <updated>2015-08-24T17:39:37-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://mariapichon.github.io/MyBlog/blog/2015/08/24/ruby</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>This week was very good. We started working on our group projects! It has been really interesting ! <!--more--> I&rsquo;m looking forward to what the final outcome is going to look like. I was struggling with my part of the project but I looked at examples and was finally able to do part of my job! For me it was hard because I feel like I don&rsquo;t have much imagination and I also didn&rsquo;t want to come up with something that seemed stupid so looking at the examples really helped me!!  Also Akbar moved to New York this wednesday so it&rsquo;s going to be interesting to see how this group project works out!</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mock Interviews]]></title>
    <link href="http://mariapichon.github.io/MyBlog/blog/2015/08/16/mock-interviews/"/>
    <updated>2015-08-16T11:48:39-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://mariapichon.github.io/MyBlog/blog/2015/08/16/mock-interviews</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>This week has gone well! My Portfolio website is starting to look good. I have managed to get the layout that I wanted this whole time and added a pdf of my resume incase anyone wants to download it. <!--more-->Although I&rsquo;m liking it I still feel like it&rsquo;s too simple and is missing something but I don&rsquo;t know what to add to it or What to do with it. I also got a slideshow that I want to use for my projects working but I don&rsquo;t know how to add it to my portfolio so hopefully I get that working! I have learned a lot! and have also experienced what I could be doing if I get an internship/job related to this job because two graduates of the last cohort visited us and gave us an example of what they have been doing in their internship with drones! I also learned a lot about what to do in interviews ! Although the mock interviews we had this week were scary they gave me a lot of knowledge and I received great tips on what to do to give a great impression.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Catching Up]]></title>
    <link href="http://mariapichon.github.io/MyBlog/blog/2015/08/10/catching-up/"/>
    <updated>2015-08-10T11:38:33-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://mariapichon.github.io/MyBlog/blog/2015/08/10/catching-up</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>This weeek has been going really well! I have been getting a lot of work done! <!--more--> Although I got lots of work done this week I didn&rsquo;t geet enough time to finish all of my projects because I worked this whole weekend from morning to night and got home really tired. Although I catched up on many things that weren&rsquo;t complete I&rsquo;m now behind on newer projects because I have been having trouble comprehending them.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Class Reflection and Frustrations]]></title>
    <link href="http://mariapichon.github.io/MyBlog/blog/2015/08/01/class-reflection-and-frustrations/"/>
    <updated>2015-08-01T11:07:33-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://mariapichon.github.io/MyBlog/blog/2015/08/01/class-reflection-and-frustrations</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>I think that overall I have had a good progress. In order to stay in good standing I plan to keep attending class everyday and ask as many questions as I can whenever i&rsquo;m confused. <!--more--> I will also try to help my classmates as much as I can because that not only helps them understand the material but it also helps clarify my understanding and solidify my knowledge.</p>

<p>This week was tough. I feel like we are getting a lot of projects and not enough time, which stresses me because once I get home it should be time to relax because we already spent 9 hours in class but instead we have to use the time to keep studying in order to finish all the assignments we are asssigned in time. That&rsquo;s why I was glad when we were announced that chapter 4 won&rsquo;t be due until next week because it lessens the load a bit and gives me a little more time to finish everything else.</p>

<p>I have also been learning a lot! about css which I&rsquo;m hoping I will be able to implement into the coding of the upcoming projects and practice a little more.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[More HTML and CSS]]></title>
    <link href="http://mariapichon.github.io/MyBlog/blog/2015/07/26/more-html-and-css/"/>
    <updated>2015-07-26T10:54:00-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://mariapichon.github.io/MyBlog/blog/2015/07/26/more-html-and-css</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>This week was really interisting. I keep learning so much information about HTML and CSS and I&rsquo;m very excited for the final outcome of our portfolios! Chapter03 has been tough but I think that with a little more practice I will be able to understand it better.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[HTML and CSS]]></title>
    <link href="http://mariapichon.github.io/MyBlog/blog/2015/07/17/html-and-css/"/>
    <updated>2015-07-17T10:31:27-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://mariapichon.github.io/MyBlog/blog/2015/07/17/html-and-css</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>This week has been great! I find learning about HTML and CSS a lot easier than JavaScript. I find all the coding behind a webpage/website very interesting. I&rsquo;m a little confused about when to use JavaScript and HTML but I still have learned alot! I didn&rsquo;t have time to work on chapter 3 but I will be working on it on Monday.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[More Java, Graphic Design and UX Conference]]></title>
    <link href="http://mariapichon.github.io/MyBlog/blog/2015/07/06/more-java-graphic-design-and-ux-conference/"/>
    <updated>2015-07-06T10:25:01-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://mariapichon.github.io/MyBlog/blog/2015/07/06/more-java-graphic-design-and-ux-conference</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Monday 7/6/2015: Today we finished our Scrum board workshop! It was really interesting seeing how much we can get done in just two days and the amazing things we can do to working as a team!</p>

<p>Tuesday 7/7/2015: I finally finished working on Worksheet 2. It was really challenging and I still have some questions but I am feeling much more confident about javascript and I think that if we review later and go over the questions I will get a even deeper understanding!</p>

<p>Wednesday 7/8/2015: Today was a really fun day! We had a Graphic design workshop and learned about the different properties involving it and got to create some patterns to exercise our understanding on them. I also reviewed how to push our blog posts because I had forgotten how to do it.</p>

<p>Friday 7/10/2015: Today was a really fun day! It was really informative and interesting. My favourite speech was the one that was given about generation z. Unfortunately I was only able to stay at the conference for four hours because I had to go to work afterwards but I loved the whole experience and am looking forward to something Similar again!</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Loops]]></title>
    <link href="http://mariapichon.github.io/MyBlog/blog/2015/06/29/loops/"/>
    <updated>2015-06-29T10:19:39-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://mariapichon.github.io/MyBlog/blog/2015/06/29/loops</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>This week I learned a lot!I have progressed a lot in worksheet 2 but there&rsquo;s still a couple thing that i don&rsquo;t completely understand like loops. I also had lots of fun doing our first workshop. Everyone took it seriously and participated. I learned what a scrum board does and how it works. Overall week 3 was good.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript and Mood Boards]]></title>
    <link href="http://mariapichon.github.io/MyBlog/blog/2015/06/26/javascript-and-mood-boards/"/>
    <updated>2015-06-26T10:13:07-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://mariapichon.github.io/MyBlog/blog/2015/06/26/javascript-and-mood-boards</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>This week I have learned a lot! We began learning about Java and a lot of the stuff we learned in chapter one is related to math. This made it very easy to learn because I think that Math is my best subject and I LOVE algebra! It was kind of challenging because we had to solve it by order of operations and there were some in which I didn&rsquo;t know which part I had to do first. We also began doing our mood boards which I found lots of fun! I created my board on pinterest which I already had experience doing. The pictures that I selected to have in my board involved fashion, music, nature, quotes and my family! overall this week went well, but We just started working on chapter 2 of our workbook and i&rsquo;m struggling a bit with it .</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to My Blog]]></title>
    <link href="http://mariapichon.github.io/MyBlog/blog/2015/06/19/welcome-to-my-blog/"/>
    <updated>2015-06-19T10:03:53-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://mariapichon.github.io/MyBlog/blog/2015/06/19/welcome-to-my-blog</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>I have learned a lot this week! I learned about markdown, pwd, hostname, mkdir, cd, ls, rmdir, touch, cp I have also learned how to install apps on my computer using codes.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
